let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        theme: "",
        question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Dog'?",
        answer: "A. Köpek",
        options: [
            "A. Köpek",
            "B. Köpük",
            "C. Tanrı",
            "D. Kopuk"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        theme: "",
        question: "What is the Turkish word for 'How'?",
        answer: "C. Nasıl",
        options: [
            "A. Nerede",
            "B. Niçin",
            "C. Nasıl",
            "D. Ne"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        theme: "",
        question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Lion'?",
        answer: "D. Aslan",
        options: [
            "A. Kaplan",
            "B. Sırtlan",
            "C. Limon",
            "D. Aslan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        theme: "",
        question: "What is the Turkish word for 'After'?",
        answer: "B. Sonra",
        options: [
            "A. Önce",
            "B. Sonra",
            "C. Arka",
            "D. İlk"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        theme: "",
        question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Computer'?",
        answer: "C. Bilgisayar",
        options: [
            "A. Kompakt",
            "B. Bilgi",
            "C. Bilgisayar",
            "D. Derleyici"
        ]
    },
    // {
    //     numb: 6,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Door'?",
    //     answer: "D. Kapı",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Dur",
    //         "B. Dar",
    //         "C. Kap",
    //         "D. Kapı"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 7,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Cat'?",
    //     answer: "B. Kedi",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Ket",
    //         "B. Kedi",
    //         "C. Kat",
    //         "D. Köpek"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 8,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Car'?",
    //     answer: "B. Araba",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Kar",
    //         "B. Araba",
    //         "C. Kan",
    //         "D. Arama"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 9,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Fish'?",
    //     answer: "A. Balık",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Balık",
    //         "B. Fiş",
    //         "C. Alık",
    //         "D. İş"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 10,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Monkey'?",
    //     answer: "C. Maymun",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Para",
    //         "B. Manav",
    //         "C. Maymun",
    //         "D. Mayıs"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 11,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Password'?",
    //     answer: "C. Şifre",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Pasaport",
    //         "B. Paspas",
    //         "C. Şifre",
    //         "D. Pasola"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 12,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Time'?",
    //     answer: "A. Zaman",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Zaman",
    //         "B. Zarf",
    //         "C. Saman",
    //         "D. Zamazingo"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 13,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Dance'?",
    //     answer: "C. Dans",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Denk",
    //         "B. Dank",
    //         "C. Dans",
    //         "D. Mızrak"
    //     
    // }
 // {
    //     numb: 14,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Hello'?",
    //     answer: "D. Merhaba",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Hoş Geldiniz",
    //         "B. İyi Günler",
    //         "C. Güle Güle",
    //         "D. Merhaba"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 15,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Welcome'?",
    //     answer: "A. Hoş Geldiniz",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Hoş Geldiniz",
    //         "B. Bu Akşam",
    //         "C. Dün",
    //         "D. Mızrak"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 16,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Ability'?",
    //     answer: "C. Yetenek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Yukarıda",
    //         "B. Dernek",
    //         "C. Yetenek",
    //         "D. Aslında"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 17,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'About'?",
    //     answer: "B. Hakkında",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Açıkça",
    //         "B. Hakkında",
    //         "C. Eylem",
    //         "D. Okumak"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 18,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Bed'?",
    //     answer: "C. Yatak",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Banyo",
    //         "B. Kötü",
    //         "C. Yatak",
    //         "D. En İyisi"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 19,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Claim'?",
    //     answer: "A. İddia Etmek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. İddia Etmek",
    //         "B. Koç",
    //         "C. Seçmek",
    //         "D. Sınıf"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 20,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'close'?",
    //     answer: "B. Kapatmak",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Soğuk",
    //         "B. Kapatmak",
    //         "C. Toplamak",
    //         "D. Kolej"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 21,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Design'?",
    //     answer: "C. Tasarım",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Derece",
    //         "B. Fark",
    //         "C. Tasarım",
    //         "D. Ölçü"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 22,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Election'?",
    //     answer: "A. Seçim",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Seçim",
    //         "B. Ekonomik",
    //         "C. Kenar",
    //         "D. Eğitim"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 23,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Grow'?",
    //     answer: "D. Büyümek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Tahmin",
    //         "B. Nesil",
    //         "C. Hedef",
    //         "D. Büyümek"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 24,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Here'?",
    //     answer: "B. Burada",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Yüksek",
    //         "B. Burada",
    //         "C. Yardım",
    //         "D. Duymak"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 25,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'İmprove'?",
    //     answer: "C. İyileştirmek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. İnsan",
    //         "B. İçinde",
    //         "C. İyileştirmek",
    //         "D. Önemli"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 26,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Low'?",
    //     answer: "A. Düşük",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Düşük",
    //         "B. Bırakmak",
    //         "C. Yalnız",
    //         "D. Kaybetmek"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 27,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Necessary'?",
    //     answer: "C. Gerekli",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Gazete",
    //         "B. Neredeyse",
    //         "C. Gerekli",
    //         "D. İhtiyaç Duymak"
    //     ]
    // }, 
    // {
    //     numb: 28,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Official'?",
    //     answer: "C. Resmi",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Memur",
    //         "B. Ofis",
    //         "C. Resmi",
    //         "D. Okul"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 29,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Operation'?",
    //     answer: "A. Ameliyat",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Ameliyat",
    //         "B. Fırsat",
    //         "C. Seçenek",
    //         "D. Bir Zamanlar"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 30,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Participant'?",
    //     answer: "C. Katılımcı",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Parti",
    //         "B. Paketlemek",
    //         "C. Katılımcı",
    //         "D. Partner"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 31,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Public'?",
    //     answer: "D. Halka Açık",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Program",
    //         "B. Profesör",
    //         "C. Gayrimenkul",
    //         "D. Halka Açık"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 32,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Rule'?",
    //     answer: "B. Kural",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Güvenli",
    //         "B. Kural",
    //         "C. Cetvel",
    //         "D. Risk"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 33,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Same'?",
    //     answer: "A. Aynı",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Aynı",
    //         "B. Biraz",
    //         "C. Nadiren",
    //         "D. Zengin"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 34,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Term'?",
    //     answer: "C. Terim",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Orada",
    //         "B. Yönelmek",
    //         "C. Terim",
    //         "D. Sonra"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 35,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Usually'?",
    //     answer: "D. Genellikle",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Kullanmak",
    //         "B. Çevirmek",
    //         "C. Anlamak",
    //         "D. Genellikle"
    //     ]
    // },
     // {
    //     numb: 36,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Value'?",
    //     answer: "D. Değer",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Silah",
    //         "B. Ağırlık",
    //         "C. Yol",
    //         "D. Değer"
    //     ]
    // },
// {
    //     numb: 37,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'West'?",
    //     answer: "B. Batı",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Tamam",
    //         "B. Batı",
    //         "C. Beyaz",
    //         "D. Hangi"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 38,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Whatever'?",
    //     answer: "B. Her Neyse",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Ne",
    //         "B. Her Neyse",
    //         "C. Nasıl",
    //         "D. Niçin"
    //     ]
    // },

// {
    //     numb: 39,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Zoom'?",
    //     answer: "C.Yakınlaşmak ",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Zebra",
    //         "B. Toplantı Yapmak",
    //         "C. Yakınlaşmak",
    //         "D. Zombi"
    //     ]
    // },
    
    // {
    //     numb: 40,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Wonder'?",
    //     answer: "A. Merak Etmek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Merak Etmek",
    //         "B. Şüphe Duymak",
    //         "C. Güzel Bulmak",
    //         "D. Hoşlanmak"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 41,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Victim'?",
    //     answer: "B. Kurban",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Ziyaret Etmek",
    //         "B. Kurban",
    //         "C. Beklemek",
    //         "D. Sorun"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 42,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Understand'?",
    //     answer: "D. Anlamak",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Hakikat",
    //         "B. Yolculuk",
    //         "C. Denemek",
    //         "D. Anlamak"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 43,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Theory'?",
    //     answer: "D. Teori",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Düşünmek",
    //         "B. Almak",
    //         "C. Takım",
    //         "D. Teori"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 44,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'teach'?",
    //     answer: "A. Öğretmek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Öğretmek",
    //         "B. Masa",
    //         "C. Öğretmen",
    //         "D. Öğrenci"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 45,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Suddenly'?",
    //     answer: "C. Aniden",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Başarılı",
    //         "B. Acı Çekmek",
    //         "C. Aniden",
    //         "D. Ders Çalışma"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 46,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Spend'?",
    //     answer: "D. Harcamak",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Bahar",
    //         "B. Sahne",
    //         "C. Konuşmak",
    //         "D. Harcamak"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 47,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Research'?",
    //     answer: "B. Araştırma",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Arama",
    //         "B. Araştırma",
    //         "C. Arama Motoru",
    //         "D. Cevap vermek"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 48,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Positive'?",
    //     answer: "A. Pozitif",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Pozitif",
    //         "B. Olumlu",
    //         "C. Tamam",
    //         "D. Güzel"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 49,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'President'?",
    //     answer: "C. Devlet Başkanı",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Şöhret",
    //         "B. Prestij",
    //         "C. Devlet Başkanı",
    //         "D. Prensip"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 50,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Outside'?",
    //     answer: "A. Dışında",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Dışında",
    //         "B. İçinde",
    //         "C. Altında",
    //         "D. Üstünde"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 51,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Myself'?",
    //     answer: "B. Kendim",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Başkası",
    //         "B. Kendim",
    //         "C. O",
    //         "D. Sen"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 52,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Member'?",
    //     answer: "C. Üye",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Askeri",
    //         "B. Milyon",
    //         "C. Üye",
    //         "D. Toplantı"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 53,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Language'?",
    //     answer: "B. Dil",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Geniş",
    //         "B. Dil",
    //         "C. Bilmek",
    //         "D. Konuşmak"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 54,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'İnvolve'?",
    //     answer: "A. İçermek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. İçermek",
    //         "B. İçinde",
    //         "C. İlginç",
    //         "D. İyileştirmek"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 55,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Healty'?",
    //     answer: "B. Sağlık",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Ambulans",
    //         "B. Sağlık",
    //         "C. Doktor",
    //         "D. Hemşire"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 56,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Goverment'?",
    //     answer: "D. Hükümet",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Kavga",
    //         "B. Yasa",
    //         "C. Kanun",
    //         "D. Hükümet"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 57,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Food'?",
    //     answer: "C. Yiyecek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. İçecek",
    //         "B. Köpek",
    //         "C. Yiyecek",
    //         "D. Kedi"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 58,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Everybody'?",
    //     answer: "B. Herkes",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Kimse",
    //         "B. Herkes",
    //         "C. Onlar",
    //         "D. Bizler"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 59,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Employee'?",
    //     answer: "D. Çalışan",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Sendikalı",
    //         "B. Müdür",
    //         "C. Patron",
    //         "D. Çalışan"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 60,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Direction'?",
    //     answer: "B. Yön",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Yer",
    //         "B. Yön",
    //         "C. Uzaklık",
    //         "D. Direk"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 61,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Cover'?",
    //     answer: "A. Örtmek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Örtmek",
    //         "B. Açmak",
    //         "C. Taklit",
    //         "D. Okumak"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 62,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'box'?",
    //     answer: "C. Kutu",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Şans",
    //         "B. Yaşam",
    //         "C. Kutu",
    //         "D. Suç"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 63,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Attention'?",
    //     answer: "D. Dikkat",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Yaklaşım",
    //         "B. Tehlike",
    //         "C. Avukat",
    //         "D. Dikkat"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 64,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Campaign'?",
    //     answer: "D. Kampanya",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Karşı",
    //         "B. Miktar",
    //         "C. Şans",
    //         "D. Kampanya"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 65,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Describe'?",
    //     answer: "C. Tanımlamak",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Kabul Etmek",
    //         "B. Eylem",
    //         "C. Tanımlamak",
    //         "D. Karşı"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 66,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Enough'?",
    //     answer: "B. Yeterli",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Görünmek",
    //         "B. Yeterli",
    //         "C. Varmak",
    //         "D. Uzak"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 67,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'General'?",
    //     answer: "B. Genel",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. General",
    //         "B. Genel",
    //         "C. Albay",
    //         "D. Normal"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 68,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'History'?",
    //     answer: "A. Tarih",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Tarih",
    //         "B. Milattan Önce",
    //         "C. Tarihi Eser",
    //         "D. İlk Çağ"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 69,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'İndeed'?",
    //     answer: "C. Aslında",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Çevre",
    //         "B. İlginç",
    //         "C. Aslında",
    //         "D. Çevreci"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 70,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Line'?",
    //     answer: "C. Çizgi",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. lime",
    //         "B. Aslan",
    //         "C. Çizgi",
    //         "D. Kaplan"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 71,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Maybe'?",
    //     answer: "A. Belki",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Belki",
    //         "B. Sonra",
    //         "C. Neyse",
    //         "D. peki"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 72,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Network'?",
    //     answer: "D. Ağ",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Bilgi",
    //         "B. Çalışma",
    //         "C. İnternet",
    //         "D. Ağ"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 73,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Owner'?",
    //     answer: "D. Sahip",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Satıcı",
    //         "B. Zengin",
    //         "C. Yoksul",
    //         "D. Sahip"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 74,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'probably'?",
    //     answer: "A. Muhtemelen",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Muhtemelen",
    //         "B. Problem",
    //         "C. Profesonel",
    //         "D. Uzman"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 75,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Scientist'?",
    //     answer: "C. Bilim İnsanı",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Fizikçi",
    //         "B. Kimyacı",
    //         "C. Bilim İnsanı",
    //         "D. Biyolog"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 76,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Total'?",
    //     answer: "B. Toplam",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Petrol",
    //         "B. Toplam",
    //         "C. Çıkarım",
    //         "D. Elde Kalan"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 77,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Yard'?",
    //     answer: "D. Avlu",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Plaj",
    //         "B. Arena",
    //         "C. Park",
    //         "D. Avlu"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 78,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Support'?",
    //     answer: "A. Destek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Destek",
    //         "B. Spor",
    //         "C. Danışman",
    //         "D. Danışan"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 79,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Reduce'?",
    //     answer: "D. Azaltmak",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Çıkartmak",
    //         "B. Toplamak",
    //         "C. Çoğaltmak",
    //         "D. Azaltmak"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 80,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Population'?",
    //     answer: "C. Nüfus",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Çoğunluk",
    //         "B. Evrim",
    //         "C. Nufüs",
    //         "D. Popüler"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 81,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Notice'?",
    //     answer: "B. Fark Etmek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Olumsuz",
    //         "B. Fark Etmek",
    //         "C. Burun",
    //         "D. Not Defteri"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 82,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Material'?",
    //     answer: "D. Malzeme",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Kuvvet",
    //         "B. Yabancı",
    //         "C. Zemin",
    //         "D. Malzeme"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 83,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Knowledge'?",
    //     answer: "A. Bilgi",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Bilgi",
    //         "B. Buzdolabı",
    //         "C. Veri",
    //         "D. Bıçak"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 84,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'İmagine'?",
    //     answer: "A. Hayal Etmek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Hayal Etmek",
    //         "B. Görsel",
    //         "C. İmaj",
    //         "D. Marjinal"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 85,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Heavy'?",
    //     answer: "C. Ağır",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Sağlıklı",
    //         "B. Kolay",
    //         "C. Ağır",
    //         "D. Nesil"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 86,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Future'?",
    //     answer: "B. Gelecek",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Unutmak",
    //         "B. Gelecek",
    //         "C. Meyve",
    //         "D. Umut"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 87,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Focus'?",
    //     answer: "B. Odaklanmak",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Sahip Olmak",
    //         "B. Odaklanmak",
    //         "C. Sevmek",
    //         "D. Mutlu"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 88,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Enjoy'?",
    //     answer: "A. Keyif Almak",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Keyif Almak",
    //         "B. İlgi Duymak",
    //         "C. Zorluk Yaşamak",
    //         "D. Mutlu Olmak"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 89,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'Husband'?",
    //     answer: "D. Koca",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Beyefendi",
    //         "B. Hanımefendi",
    //         "C. Eş",
    //         "D. Koca"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 90,
    //     theme: "",
    //     question: "What is the Turkish word for 'İnterview'?",
    //     answer: "C. Röportaj",
    //     options: [
    //         "A. Ulus",
    //         "B. Uluslararası",
    //         "C. Ropörtaj",
    //         "D. Medeniyet"
    //     ]
    // },
]
